Finding aid for George William Cushing Papers and sound recordings, 1942-1955
Bentley Historical Library
- In Our Opinion: recordings of programs, 7 in. reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips
  - 1946 (Box 4)
    - OPA, 1946 July 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-74-1]; (Guests: Fred L. Riggin, Mayor Harry L. Gillow, Tom Ferris, Superintendent. Howard D. Crull, Lou A. Weil, Mrs. M.O. Hitchings, Mrs. Raymond Wurzel.)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1946 August 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-75-1]; (Senator Arthur Vandenberg)
    - What Is The Situation In Germany Today?, 1946 September 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-76-1]; (The State of Affairs on Germany; Guests: Dr. James K. Pollock.)
    - Shall Objects Of Historical Interest Be Preserved or Torn Down To Make Way For Modern Improvements?, 1946 September 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-77-1]; (On the topic of the preservation of historic buildings. Guests: George F. Emery, Commissioner Milton C. Selendar, Edgar P. Richardson, William Woolfenden.)
    - Can We Do Business With Russia?, 1946 September 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-78-1]; (Can we live with Soviet Russia? Guests: Dr. Charles Prince, Grant Arnold.)
    - Shall Criminals Be Punished or Treated For Their Behavior?, 1946 October 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-79-1]; (Guests: Austin MacCormick, Warden Walter Wallack, Dr. Miriam Van Waters, Dr. Robert M. Lindner, Hon. Ira W. Jayne.)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1946 October 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-80-1]; (Senator Arthur Vandenberg)
    - Discussion of the Three State Amendments to be Voted on in the November 5 Elections, 1946 October 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-81-1]; (Guests: George Edwards, Charles C. Lockwood.)
    - The Inside Story on the Reporting of Radio News by Three Great Press Associations, 1946 October 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-82-1]; (Guests: Tom O'Neil, Robert Brown, Phil Newsome)
    - Is The Present Curriculum Of Our Schools Suited To The Present Day Needs Of Our Boys And Girls?, 1946 November 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-83-1]; (Suitability of Public School Curriculums; Guests: Dr. Eugene B. Elliott, Dr. Earl Kelly, Dr. Owen Emmons.)
    - Students Discuss The Present Curriculum Of Our Schools, 1946 November 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-84-1]; (Guests: Joe Cyr (Fordson High), Maureen Scanlon (Fordson High), Donald Muench (Northwestern High), Patricia Cawley (Northwestern High), Majorie Aiken (Highland Park Jr. College), Tom Frank (University of Michigan), Byron Williams (Wayne University), James Jones (Wayne University).)
    - Our Public Schools, 1946 November 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-85-1]; (Guests: Mrs. Kathleen Lardie, Miss Margaret Mary Kerwin, Mrs. Laberyl Hayller, Miss Agnes Crow.)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1946 November 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-86-1]; (Appearance of Senator Arthur Vandenberg on the George Cushing radio program.)
    - Labor Court, 1946 December 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-87-1]; (Senator Ferguson and his poposal for a Labor Court; Guests: Senator Homer Ferguson.)
  - 1947
    - "Religion in Affairs of Business and Politics", January 5, 1947 (Box 5)
      (Guests: Charles P. Taft (President of the Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1947 January 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-89-1]; (Tape 1 of Senator Vandenberg speaking.)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1947 January 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-90-1]; (Tape 2; of Senator Vandenberg speaking.)
    - Law in Relation to Problems of Labor and Management, 1947 January 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-91-1]; (Labor Legislation Part 1; Guests: Ernest Goodman, Leon Cousens, Frank Cooper, Max Veach.)
    - Labor Legislation; [Law in Relation to Problems of Labor and Management], 1947 January 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-92-1]; (Labor Legislation Part 2; Guests: Ernest Goodman, Leon Cousens, Frank Cooper, Max Veach.)
    - "Labor Legislation", January 26, 1947 (Box 5)
      (Guests: Senator Joseph H. Ball, Nelson Cruikshank.)
      (The surface of the disc was bad)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1947 February 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-94-1]; (Tape 1; Labor Legislation Part 3;)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1947 February 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-95-1]; (Tape 2 of Senator Vandenberg speaking.)
    - Investigations by Governmental Committees, 1947 February 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-96-1]; (Guests: Senator Homer Ferguson, Senator William F. Knowland.)
    - The Situation in China Today, 1947 February 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-97-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Rt. Rev. Quentin K. Y. Huang, Bishop of Kumming, Miss Maxine Westfall.)
    - State Budget, 1947 March 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-98-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring John Perkins, State Budget Director)
    - Universal Military Training, 1947 March 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-99-1]; (In Our Opinion program with guests Lieutenant General Raymond S. McLain, Professor Alfred H. Kelly, and Trainee Leonard A. Grushko discuss universal military training and the end of the Selective Service Act.)
    - Detroit House of Correction, 1947 April 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-100-1]; (In Our Opinion program feautiring guests Superintendent A. Blake Gillies of the Detroit House of Corrections, Miss Grace Travis of the Women's Division of the Detroit House of Corrections, Mrs. Fern Dull, and "Pat", a female inmate of 8 years.)
    - Report on the German Situation, 1947 April 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-101-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring guests Professor of Political Science at the University of Michigan and Dr. James K. Pollock discussing the state of Germany after the war.)
    - Report from Turkey and Greece, 1947 April 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-102-1]; (In Our Opinion program detailing Senator Homer Ferguson's trip to the Middle East, including Palestine, Jerusalem, and Cairo.)
    - College Campus Problems, 1947 May 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-103-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring guests Richard Roder (Student President of the Michigan Union), Paul Harsha (Editor of the Michigan Daily), Robert Wiese (student Representative, Board of Athletics), and Haskel Coplin (Past President of the Student Legislature) discussing what academic freedom is for college students.)
    - Infiltration of Communists in the United States, 1947 May 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 5)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-104-1]; (In Our Opinion program feautiring Pulitzer Prize winner Frederick Woltman and Charles Hasperhoven, Public Relations Director for the Govt Information Service in the Netherlands East Indies discussing the influence of Communism.)
    - Michigan State Class of 1912 35th Reunion, 1947 June 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-105-1]; (In Our Opinion program feautirng the Michigan State Class of 1912 35th Reunion. Guests include Glen Stewart (Director of Alumni Relations), and former students Mrs. Thomas Gunson, Ralph Goodell, C. H. Dickinson, H. Lee Bancroft, E. E. Hotchin, B. P. Pattison, R. B. Delvin, Bess Howe Geagley, and Leon C. Exelby.)
    - Turkey, 1947 June 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-106-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring guests Mrs. Fahrinnisa Seden, a Turkish nurse who trained at the Henry Ford Hopsital and Dr. Roy D. McClure, Surgeon and Chief of Henry Ford Hospital, discussing the state of medical care in Turkey.)
    - The Family Doctor, 1947 June 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-107-1]; (In Our Opinion program feauturing guests Dr. William G. Wight, Dr. Frederick B. Wight, Mayor John Kaatz, Frank Andre, Fred Andre (grandson of above), Clarence Reed (farmer), Mrs. George Barth, D. A. McIntyre (Detroit), Mrs. Dora Martin, Miss Pearl McDonald, George Cavanaugh, John Patterson, Mary McCabe (nurse), Mina Mackman (nurse)))
    - Traffic Safety featuring the Michigan State Police, 1947 July 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-108-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring guests Capt. C. J. Scavarda, Sergeant C. F. Van Blankensteyn, Mr. Orrin Lucas, Sergeant William Bouck, Dispatcher McBride, (Reports from: Jackson, Rockwood, Detroit, Bay City, State Trooper at Pinconning))
    - Father Flanagan's Report on Japan, 1947 July 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-109-1]; (In Our Opinion program feauturing guest Father Flanagan)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1947 September 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-110-1]; (In Our Opinion program feauturing George C. Marshall, Secretary of State, and Senator Arthur Vandenberg discussing the Inter-American Conference in Rio de Janeiro.)
    - The Hillsdale County Fair, 1947 September 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-111-1]; (Guests: Harry B. Kelley, Lester Rogers, Sherman Young, Miss Blanche Wolcott, Ivan Maystead, Blair Woodman, Marshall Wells)
    - Hickory Corners, 1947 September 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-112-1]; (Guests: Governor Kim Sigler, Oscar Harrington, C. F. Rennels, Vere Williams, Ralph Starring, C. M. McCrary.)
    - Candidates for Mayor of Detroit, 1947 October 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-113-1]; (George Cushing interviewing Detroit Mayoral candidates; Guests: Mayor Edward J. Jeffries, Jr., Eugene Van Antwerp, Gerald Adams, Herman Benson, George O. Cornell, Howard Lerner, Joseph J. Mogor, Alfred C. Semande.)
    - Desperate Situation in Europe, 1947 October 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-114-1]; (Discussing the situation in Europe following the war; Guests: George Romney.)
    - "Youth Festival at Prague", October 19, 1947 (Box 6)
      (Guests: Eleanor Roberts, Harris Wofford, Jr.)
      (typescript of program in box 1)
    - Situation in Europe, 1947 October 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-116-1]; (In Our Opinion Program discussing post-war Europe; Guests: Eugene C. Pulliam, Mrs. Nina Pulliam.)
    - Negro and Communism, 1947 November 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-117-1]; (Guests: Ulysses W. Boykin, Edward W. Swan, Andrew J. Smith, Fred A. Allen, L. C. Blount.)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1947 November 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-118-1]; (Senator Arthur Vandenberg speaking at the University of Michigan on Dutch and American relationships and Dutch American heritage, featuring Dutch Ambassador Mr. Eelco Nicolaas Van Kleffens)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1947 November 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-119-1]; (Appearance of Senator Arthur Vandenberg on the George Cushing radio program.)
    - American Education in Far East, 1947 November 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-120-1]; (Guests: Lowell Thomas, President Bayard Dodge.)
    - Uncle Sam in the role of Santa Claus, 1947 December 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-121-1]; (On the topic of foreign aid; Guests: Senator Homer Ferguson and Representative Frank B. Keefe)
    - Disabled War Veterans Employment Problems, 1947 December 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-122-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program on the topic of disabled vetereans employment. Guests: Frank X. Martel, Howard K. Kelley, Robert A. Oliver.)
  - 1948
    - "Michigan Problems as Seen from Arizona", January 18, 1948 (Box 6)
      (Guests: Governor Kim Sigler)
    - Present Situation in Greece, 1948 January 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-124-1]; (In Our Opinion Radio Program discussing the insurgency and war in Greece. Guests: Dr. Ernest W. Riggs)
    - The Kon-Tiki Raft Expedition, 1948 February 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-125-1]; (In Our Opinion Radio Program; Guests: Thor Heyerdahl.)
    - Michigan Highway Plan, 1948 February 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-126-1]; (Guests: Thomas H. MacDonald, J. P. Buckley, Don B. Smith.)
    - American Legion Discusses 'Americanism', 1948 February 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-127-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program; Guests: Arthur Clark, Herman Luhrs, Victor Galloway, Floyd Haight, William Malloy, Leo Navarre, Hugh H. Neale, Wilbur Brucker, Joseph Kornfedder, Walter Scott.)
    - Britain, 1948 February 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-128-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing the situation in the United Kingdom following the war; Guests: Colonel James Riley Holt Hutchinson.)
    - Cruises in the Persian Gulf, etc (Guests: Commander Alan Villiers, George Pierrot), 1948 March 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-129-1]; (In Our Opinion program feauturing guests Commander Alan Villiers and George Pierrot)
    - Communist Activities in the Schools, 1948 March 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-130-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Governor Kim Sigler, President Alexander G. Ruthven, President David D. Henry, President John A. Hannah.)
    - Inroads Made by Communism into American Life and Business, 1948 March 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-131-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program with George Cushing featuring guests: William Umstaddt, Dr. Maurice Lieber, Harold S. Vincent, Don S. Cordray.)
    - Detroit Fire Department, 1948 March 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-132-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Chief Ninnian C. Higby, Richard F. Reaume, Jr., Commissioner Paxton Mendelsohn, Commissioner J. L. Mahon, Chief Kendall, (Members of Fire Dept.: Orel, Beer, Galbraith, Morske, Holdhouse, St. John, Vincent), T. Curtis McKenzie)
    - Conditions in France, 1948 March 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-133-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Edward Cruskin, David Schonbrun, Jeffery Parsons (from Paris), Patrick Walberg, Pierre Crenesse.)
    - Problems Today that Worry Mothers, 1948 May 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-134-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mrs. LeRoy E. Cowles, Mrs. Byron J. Chambers, Mrs. John C. Henderson, Mrs. Ulysses Boykin.)
    - Situation in Europe Today, 1948 May 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-135-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: W. H. Lawrence, Foreign Correspondent, New York Times.)
    - Communism in Schools, 1948 May 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-136-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Russell H. Wilson (Superintendent Alpena Public Schools), Otto W. Haisley (Superintendent Ann Arbor Public Schools), Herman L. Shibler (Superintendent Highland Park School), George T. Cantrick (Superintendent Monroe Public Schools))
    - Michigan State College Students, 1948 June 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-137-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Dr. John A. Hannah (Pres. MSC), Tom King (Director Alumni Relations), Miss Ruth Meinke (Detroit), Miss Fay Flakely (Gibralter), Rollie Young (Lansing), Don Borgeson (Chicago, IL), Elliott Fritz (Schnectady, NY))
    - Delegates from Sweden, 1948 June 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-138-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. Allan Kastrup (GM Swedish News Exchange), Mr. Kridman (Swedish Adult Educational), Mr. Kugelberg (Pres. Swedish Employers Confederation))
    - Conditions in Japan, 1948 September 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 6)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-139-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Bunshiro Suzuki (Japanese editor of Reader's Digest in Japan))
    - Odd Jobs, Inc., 1948 October 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-140-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: John Gilmore, Jim Wood, Melvin Earegood, Elvin Wood, Mrs. Al Rones.)
    - Miscellaneous topics October 5,1948, 1948 October 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-141-1]; (In Our Opinion program Cancer research and updating the state of cancer research. Guests include Dr. Detlev Bronk, President Elect of Johns Hopskins University, Dr. Gordon H. Scott, Acting Dean of Wayne University Colelge of Medicine, and unnamed Drs. Nelson and Meter (?))
    - Airport Developments, 1948 October 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-142-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: James C. Buckley (Director-Airport Devel. NY Port Authority), Col. J. Victor Dallen (Pres. Airport Oprs' Council Philadelphia), Ken Smith (Capitol Airlines), Jack Tompkins (American Airlines), Eugene Fryhoff (Dir. Detroit Metropolitan Aviation Authority))
    - Conditions in Korea, 1948 October 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-143-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Dr. Frank L. Eversull (Educator, Author, Lecturer))
    - Everyday Religion, 1948 October 31; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-144-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Dr. Don Tullis, Worth Kramer.)
    - Adventures of a Sea Raider, 1948 November 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-145-1]; (In Our Opinion Radio Program featuring guests: Count Felix von Luckner.)
    - Reasons Behind the Negro Vote, 1948 November 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-146-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Rev. Theodore S. Boone (Rep. Co-ord. Com of Mich.), Rev. Robert L. Bradby, Jr. (National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Pres.), Ulysses W. Boykin (Editor Detroit Tribune), Victor Hicks (Wayne County Demo Com.))
    - Defense Plans for Michigan, 1948 November 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-147-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing civil defense, featuring guests: Donald S. Leonard (Comm. Mich. State Police), John Huss (Director, Mich. Municipal League), John Witherspoon (Asst. Corp Counsel Detroit).)
    - Conditions In Europe As Seen From A Trailer, 1948 November 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-148-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Cornelius Vanderbilt, Jr. (Journalist & Lecturer))
    - North American Indians, 1948 December 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-149-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Fred Ettawagshik, Norman I. Ewing, Dr. Thomas J. Jameson, Louis A. Morago.)
    - Baby Treatment, 1948 December 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-150-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program on the subject of parenting featuring guests: Dr. Howard C. Walser, Dr. John C. Montgomery, Dr. Donald J. Barnes, Dr. James Wilson.)
    - Security (Unification of The United States Armed Services), 1948 December 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-151-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guest: S.L.A. Marshall.)
  - 1949
    - Exchange Students Back From Abroad, 1949 January 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-152-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: William Miller (U of M), Fred Keydel (Yale), Patricia Lytle (Wayne), Harvey Wiseberg (U of M), Sam Schwartz (Wayne).)
    - British Embassy Answers Vanderbilt, 1949 January 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-153-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: D.F.H. Brickell, (British Consulate General), A.N. Duckham (Agricultural Attache to Embassy, Washington D.C.))
    - China Today, 1949 January 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-154-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Professor Russell H. Fifield (U of M), Russell Barnes (Detroit News Foreign Correspondent))
    - Alcoholism, 1949 February 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-155-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing legislation for alcoholics, featuring guests: Hon. Robert W. Kenny (formerly Attorney General of California), Judge Lewis Drucker (Judge Municipal Court-Cleveland), James Montante (President Detroit Chapter -- National Lawyers Guild), Mr. X (A Member of Alcoholics Anonymous))
    - Indonesia, 1949 March 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-156-1]; (In Our Opinion program discussing Indonesia and the relationship with the Dutch. Featuring Sayid A. Almassawa (South Sumatra), Dr. Amry Vandenbosch (Univeristy of Kentucky), Russell Barnes (Foreign Correspondent Detroit News), Willard C. Wichers (Director of the Midewest Division of the Netherlands Information Bureau from Holland, Mich.))
    - Child Welfare, 1949 March 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-157-1]; (In Our Opinion program discussing child welfare featuring guests Mrs. Dermot Morrah (British Magistrate), Miss Evangeline Schibley (Detroit Council of Social Agencies))
    - Interview with Monk from Burma, 1949 March 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-158-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring Lokanatha, a Burmese Buddhist monk.)
    - Candidates for School Board, 1949 April 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-159-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring the 6 Detroit Board of Education candidates Louise C. Grace, Patrick V. McNamara, Frank A. Gorman, James H. Lincoln, Jane Lovejoy, and Richard A. MacRae)
    - Conditions in Far East (Easter), 1949 April 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)